>> Jem Young: 我们刚刚收到了我们的 Express 应用程序。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: We just got
our Express app written.
有一个丢失的括号，我通过文本编辑巧妙地添加到其中，
There was a missing parentheses which I
have subtly added in there via text edit,
把它扔进去了
threw it in there.
但现在，让我们继续运行，运行该应用程序。
But now, let's go ahead and
run that, run that app.
所以我要切换，我可以说节点 app.js。
So I'm going to switch over and
I can say node app.js.
嘿它在跑凉快
Hey, it's running, cool.
现在怎么办
Now what?
我们去网站吧
Let's go to the website.
jemisbest.com 请刷新该文件，等待第二次。
And jemisbest.com,
refresh that, wait a second.
不执行任何操作，但应用程序正在运行。
Not doing anything, but
the app is running.
发生什么事了
What's going on now?
>> 演讲者 2: 您需要在正确的端口上运行吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: You need to
run it on the correct port?
>> Jem Young: 是，我们有，但缺省端口为端口 80。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yes, we do, but
the default port is port 80.
但我想知道我们能否完成 3000口
But I wonder if we can do port 3000.
现在开始工作了
Now it's working.
但这不方便
But that's not convenient.
我们无法构建应用程序并表示， hey ，转至 jemis.theby 或
We cann't build an app and say,
hey, go to jemis.thebest or
很棒但你得去港口 3000
jemisthebest, but
you gotta go to port 3000.
我妈妈会喜欢的是什么港口
Cuz my mom's gonna be like, what's a port?
这不起作用。
And that doesn't work.
因此，我们需要以某种方式将流量定向到端口 80。
So we need to somehow direct
that traffic to port 80.
我们拿到了域名我们拿到了 IP
Cuz we got the domain, we got the IP,
我们让 Nginx 跑了但是我们还是要把 Nginx 连接到 Express
we've got Nginx running, but
we still need to connect Nginx to Express.
接下来我们要做的就是调 Nginx
So this what we're gonna do next,
we're gonna tune Nginx so
它指向正确的端口。
that it points to the correct port.
我们要用指令那个奇怪的词我之前用过
To that we're gonna use directives,
that weird word I used earlier.
我们要用 proxy_pass 指令
We're gonna use the proxy_pass directive.
这就意味着我们要委托书
And all that means is
we're gonna proxy pass,
我们要去代理所有车辆的流量
we're going to proxy all the traffic
from that's going to / which is
在不同端口上的实际节点服务器的常规根域。
the general root domain to the actual
Node server on a different port.
那就走吧
So let's go and do that.
这一变化很短。
And this change is fairly short.
我们将再次编辑 Nginx 配置。
We're going to edit that
Nginx configuration again.
因此， sudo vi /etc/nginx/sites-available/default。
So sudo vi
/etc/nginx/sites-available/default.
然后我们要向下滚动到那个位置指令
And then we're going to scroll
down to that location directive,
删除其中的所有内容，然后将 proxy_pass 输入到其中。
delete out everything in there,
and then proxy_pass into it.
>> 扬声器 2: 在此处放置专用密钥，还是专用密钥?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: You put the private
key here, or the private key?
你放进去，密码，是你给用户的吗 ?
Do you put in, for the password,
is it the one that you, for the user?
>> Jem Young: 这是您创建该用户时设置的任何用户 ( sudo 用户) 。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: It's whatever you set when
you created that user, that sudo user.
>> 扬声器 3: 对不起，在什么部分下 ?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Sorry, under what section?
>> Jem Young: 在位置伪指令中。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: In the location directive.
所以，向下滚动，它会有一些类似的东西，让我来。
So scroll down and it'll have
something like, actually, let me.
我就 - > 众议长 3: 文件?
I'll just-
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Files?
>> Jem Young: 是的，只是撤销。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yeah, just undo.
因此， " 撤销" ，因此向下滚动到此处。
So Undo, so scroll down to here.
然后删除这些文件。
And then just delete these files.
因此，我将使用双 d 删除，然后切换到插入方式和选项卡。
So I'm going to use double d to delete,
then switch to insert mode and tab in.
我要说 proxy_pass。
I'm going to say proxy_pass.
因此，通过此 proxy_pass 伪指令，我们所讲的是，嘿，
So with this proxy_pass directive,
all we're telling it is, hey,
任何进入 / 或我们现在都只有一个的请求
any request that comes in to / or,
well, we only have one right now.
所以任何提出的要求，我们就提出这个要求，
So any request that comes in,
let's just forward that request and
让我们的 Node 应用程序处理它，在另一个端口上。
let our Node application handle it,
and on a different port.
这样，我们就不用改变港口了。
And this way,
we don't have to change ports.
我们不用在 80 口或任何东西上运行
We don't have to run it on port 80 or
anything like that.
我们可以在无限的港口上运行而不是无限的港口
We can run on infinite ports on,
well, not infinite ports,
不是无限的港口 Nginx 知道它们的处理位置
not infinite ports, and the Nginx
knows exactly where they're handled.
这样做的好处是我能跑 6 个不同的地方
And the benefit of doing something
like this is I can run six different
应用程序和
applications and
它们都在不同的港口运行它们都在同一时间运行
they all run on a different port
they're all running at the same time.
我可以将一个应用程序关闭，再带一个，我可以路由到一个数据库。
And I can take one application down, bring
another one up, I can route to a database.
我们所做的大部分都是通过 proxy_pass 指令
Most of what we're doing is gonna
be with the proxy_pass directive,
至少今天
at least for today.
>> Jem Young: 好的。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: All right.
>> Jem Young: Oops，我忘了重新启动服务器。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Oops, and
I forgot to restart the server.
所以，让我们把它写出来。
So, let's write quit out of here.
我们会说 sudo service nginx reload，或者
And we'll say,
sudo service nginx reload, or
重新启动，我不认为它很重要，很酷。
restart, I don't think it matters, cool.
如果您有错误，那么关于 Nginx 的好处是，如果您在
If you have an error, the good thing about
Nginx is if you have an error in your
配置，它将在它允许您重新启动之前抛出错误。
configuration, it will throw
an error before it lets you restart.
这样，你的 Web 服务器就能保持正常运行，这是非常好的。
So that way your web server keeps up and
running, it's pretty nice.
让我们测试确定我是否正确
And let's test to make
sure I did that correctly.
对不起忘了启动我的应用程序了
Oops, forgot to start my app back up.
>> Jem Young: Nice。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Nice.
现在，我的域已连接到在端口 80 上运行的 Express 应用程序。
So now I have my domain connected to my
Express application running on port 80.
还不错
Not bad.
如果您遇到麻烦，请不要忘记重新启动 Nginx。
If you're running into troubles,
don't forget to restart Nginx.
请不要忘记启动节点应用程序备份。
Don't forget to start your
Node application backup.
那是痛苦所以
And that's a pain, so
我们会想办法重新开始你的申请
we're gonna figure out how to get
around restarting your application.
>> 演讲者 3: 您是否提到了什么服务 ?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Did you
mention what service is?
和服务命令一样，那是什么 ?
Like the service command,
what does that do?
>> Jem Young: 不，我没有。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: No, I didn't.
谢谢你的请求
And thanks for asking.
服务是以下级别的最高级别的命令 :
Service is the highest-level command for
任何在后台运行的守护程序。
any sort of daemon running
in the background.
并非所有内容都在服务上运行。
Not everything runs on a service.
明天我们要用一个叫 systemctl的东西
Tomorrow we're gonna use
something called systemctl,
这是管理您的服务的方法，但在较低层。
which is a way of managing your services,
but at a lower layer.
但服务是一个很好的包装，更清洁。
But services is a nice wrapper,
it's much cleaner.
我们明天会看到的界面更先进
The interface we'll see
tomorrow is more advanced.
总体而言，我试着尽可能地选择最简单的事情。
And generally,
I try to pick the simplest thing possible.
但这才是服务
But that's what services is.
你可以用各种服务做很多事情。
You can do lots of things with services.
我可以将 " 节点 " 应用程序注册为后台运行的服务。
I can register my Node application as a
service that's running in the background.
这可能不是最好的方法
It's probably not the best
way to manage it.
但你一直想跑的 Nginx 之类的
But something like Nginx that
you always want running,
我们只是用一个服务指令
we just use a services command.
但问题是
But, good question.
我很吃惊这是我们第一次在我的命令下
I'm surprised this is the first one we've
gotten on any sort of commands I've
正在运行。
been running.
没事的没事的
It's okay.
怎么了
Yes?
>> 扬声器 3: 在 nginx 文件夹中，也有一个称为站点的文件夹。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: In the nginx folder, there
is a folder called sites enabled as well.
已启用站点与可用站点之间有何区别 ?
What's the difference between enabled and
available sites?
>> Jem Young: 实际上，一个 sym 链接到另一个。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Actually,
one sym links to the other.
我想说，我认为网站可以链接到已启用的站点。
I want to say, I think sites
available sym links to sites enabled.
您可以管理不同的配置。
You can manage different
configurations that way.
因此，您可以更改 Nginx 配置而不更改实际运行的内容。
So you can change Nginx configurations
without changing what's actually running.
当你想让它有它的时候，你可以复制它。
And then whenever you want it to be
available, you can just copy it over.
这就是一种方法。
And that's one way of doing it.
有一个我要说我要试试这个
There's a, I'm gonna say it,
I'm gonna try this.
nginx -t，是的。
nginx -t, yeah.
因此，您可以运行 nginx -t ，并且可以运行配置和
So you can run the nginx -t, and
that runs over your configuration and
证明一切都有道理
validates that everything makes sense.
事实上我们甚至有一些不符合道理的东西
In fact, we even have some things
in here that don't make sense,
这很奇怪因为这是默认配置
which is weird because it's
the default configuration.
但这就是启用站点与可用站点的功能。
But that's what the sites enabled
versus sites available is.
另一件事是你一般不会修改你的默认值。
And another thing is you generally
don't modify your default.
你把它每个地点都做了
You make it per site.
所以我想说最好的配置
So I'd say,
jemisthe.best configuration, and
然后具有 Nginx 配置。
then have an Nginx configuration for that.
然后我把它们全部融为一体
And then I merge them
all together into one.
但因为我们只做一个网络服务器
But because we're only
doing one web server,
这是最简单的例子这是最好的做法
and it's the simplest example,
that's the best practice.
问得好
Good question, though.
没想到你也没出现
Surprised that didn't come up either.
你们都很犀利
You all are sharp.
好了，每个人的网站上运行，我们都能让节点重新开始运行。
Okay, everybody's website up and running,
we get node back up and running.
你是有联系的
You're connected.
好，现在我们成功地做了一个网页应用。
All right, so now we've successfully
made a web application.
干得好大家
Nice job, everyone.
这是一个到达这里的旅程，但我们一起做了。
It was a journey to get here,
but we did it together.
这才是最重要的
That's what's important.